unlockphonetool.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy Unlock Phone Tool

At UnlockPhoneTool.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important.

### UnlockPhoneTool Privacy Statement

What follows is the Privacy Statement for UnlockPhoneTool.com. Please read this statement regarding our blog. If you have questions please ask us via our contact form.

### Email Addresses

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share your email with any third party. As a matter of fact, we do not collect these email addresses to begin with.

Ownership of Information

UnlockPhoneTool.com is the sole owner of any information collected on our website.

Comments/Message Boards

UnlockPhoneTool.com contains comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party and not used for any other purpose. In short, we will not send you unwanted emails.

### Push notifications

UnlockPhoneTool readers can opt in to receive push notifications every time a new article is published. We do not collect any information from you and anyone can unsubscribe at any time by following these steps.

### Email newsletters

UnlockPhoneTool readers can opt in to receive email newsletters. The email addresses collected for this are handled by Feedburner, a service by Google. We do not use your email address for anything else but sending you this newsletter. If you wish to unsubscribe, please see the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter you receive.

### Cookies, Web Beacons, and Similar Technologies

UnlockPhoneTool.com may use cookies, or similar technologies to manage users’ site preferences and ensure the site’s functionality. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our website is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

### Third Party Cookies

UnlockPhoneTool.com and its advertisers may also use ad network providers and other service providers, such as Google.com and Kontera, to help present customized content and advertisements on UnlockPhoneTool.com. These providers may use cookies, or similar technologies on your computer to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their content and advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks of web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audience.

UnlockPhoneTool.com may share certain non-personally identifiable information about you as an UnlockPhoneTool.com user (such as user age and zip code) with certain ad network and service providers, including Google.com and Kontera, to help them deliver more relevant content and advertisements through their networks. The use of cookies, or similar technologies by Google.com, Kontera, and other ad network and content providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not that of UnlockPhoneTool.com.

### Traffic Reports

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

### Legal proceedings

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but UnlockPhoneTool.com may need to disclose information when required by law.

### Links

UnlockPhoneTool.com frequently links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our website we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy.

### Notification of Changes

When UnlockPhoneTool.com makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.unlockphonetool.com/contact-us/).

Last Updated: 02/09/2014
